const contest_2_2 = [
    {
        "S/N": 1,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Haemoglobin molecule is made up of a protein part and a non-protein part. What is the name of the protein part of haemoglobin?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Globin",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Biochemistry", "Molecular Biology"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 2,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Give the oxidation state of oxygen in the ozone molecule, $\\mathrm{O}_{3}$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Zero. (Ozone is an allotrope of the element oxygen.)",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Oxidation States", "Inorganic Chemistry"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 3,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Give the current concentration in ppm of $\\mathrm{CO}_{2}$ in the earth's atmosphere.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$400 \\mathrm{ppm}$",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Environmental Chemistry", "Atmospheric Chemistry"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 4,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Find the internal energy of $10 \\mathrm{~mol}$ of a monatomic ideal gas at a temperature of $200 K$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$25 \\mathrm{~kJ}$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Thermodynamics", "Internal Energy"]
    },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 5,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "Find the magnitude of the lateral magnification a convex mirror of focal length $-20 \\mathrm{~cm}$ produces of an axial object $20 \\mathrm{~cm}$ from its vertex.",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "0.5",
    //     "calculations present": "Yes",
    //     "Subject": "Physics",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Optics", "Mirrors"]
    // },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 6,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "The impedance of an ac circuit is $50 \\Omega$ at the frequency of a signal with a rootmean-square voltage of $20 \\mathrm{~V}$. Find the root-mean-square current in the circuit when the signal is applied across it.",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "$0.4 \\mathrm{~A}$",
    //     "calculations present": "Yes",
    //     "Subject": "Physics",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Electric Circuits", "Impedance"]
    // },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 7,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "Name the important environment factor which epiphytes in the rain forest compete for?",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "Light",
    //     "calculations present": "No",
    //     "Subject": "Biology",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Ecology", "Competition"]

    // },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 8,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "The inner ear of mammals contains 2 main structures that perform 2 different functions. Name the part that is responsible for hearing.",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "The cochlea",
    //     "calculations present": "No",
    //     "Subject": "Biology",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Anatomy", "Auditory System"]
    // },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 9,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "Dilute $\\mathrm{NaOH}$ solution was added to a solution of food substance in a test tube, followed by the addition of drops of $1 \\% \\mathrm{CuSO}_{4}$ solution while shaking the test tube. The appearance of which colour would indicate the presence of protein?",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "The production of violet colouration",
    //     "calculations present": "No",
    //     "Subject": "Biology",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Biochemistry", "Protein Tests"]
    // },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 10,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "Find the sum to infinity of the series $5-5 / 3+5 / 9-5 / 27+\\ldots$",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "15/4, or 3.75\n[exponential series $a=5, r=-1 / 3, S_{\\mathrm{s}}=a /(1-r)=5 /(1+1 / 3)=15 / 4$ ]",
    //     "calculations present": "Yes",
    //     "Subject": "Mathematics",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Series", "Convergence"]
    // },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 11,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "Find the solution set of the inequality $2 x^{2}-3 x-5>0$.",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "$\\{x: x>5 / 2$, or $x<-1\\}$\n$\\left[2 x^{2}-3 x-5=(2 x-5)(x+1)>0, x>5 / 2\\right.$ or $\\left.x<-1\\right]$",
    //     "calculations present": "Yes",
    //     "Subject": "Mathematics",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Algebra", "Inequalities"]
    // },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 12,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "Find the sum in radians of the interior angles of a polygon of 17 sides.",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "$15 \\pi$ radians\n$[(n-2) \\pi=(17-2) \\pi=15 \\pi$ radians $]$",
    //     "calculations present": "Yes",
    //     "Subject": "Mathematics",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Geometry", "Polygons"]
    // }
]

export default contest_2_2